Middleboro, Mass. First Church of Middleboro records, 1702-1925.
Congregational Library & Archives
- Membership records, 1741 1880; 1741-1880; 34 Folders
  - Membership: N-O, 1771 1859; 1771-1859 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Oliver, Peter Jr., 1771 (Box 2, Folder 12, Item 4)
    - Oliver, Sarah, 1771 (Box 2, Folder 12, Item 5)
    - Orcutt, Harriet, 1840 (Box 2, Folder 12, Item 6)
    - Orrington, Mary Ann, 1838 (Box 2, Folder 12, Item 7)
    - Osgood, Julia H., 1859 (Box 2, Folder 12, Item 8)
  - Membership: P, 1757 1863; 1757-1863 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Paddock, Lydia, 1807 (Box 2, Folder 13, Item 1)
    - Penniman, Virtue M., 1863 (Box 2, Folder 13, Item 2)
    - Perkins, Eunice, 1842 (Box 2, Folder 13, Item 3)
    - Perkins, John, 1815 (Box 2, Folder 13, Item 4)
    - Perkins, Lothrop, 1809 (Box 2, Folder 13, Item 5)
    - Perkins, Mercy, 1809 (Box 2, Folder 13, Item 6)
    - Phinney, Sarah, 1786 (Box 2, Folder 13, Item 7)
    - Pickens, Caroline, 1836 (Box 2, Folder 13, Item 8)
    - Pickens, Ebenezer, 1829 (Box 2, Folder 13, Item 9)
    - Pickens, Mary, 1829 (Box 2, Folder 13, Item 10)
    - Pierce, Charles, 1824 (Box 2, Folder 13, Item 11)
    - Pierce, Experience, 1800 (Box 2, Folder 13, Item 12)
    - Pool, Lydia, 1829 (Box 2, Folder 13, Item 13)
    - Pool, Samuel, 1829 (Box 2, Folder 13, Item 13)
    - Porter, Mercy, 1794 (Box 2, Folder 13, Item 14)
    - Porter, Sarah, 1813 (Box 2, Folder 13, Item 15)
    - Porter (Noyes), Sibil, 1808 1838; 1808-1838 (Box 2, Folder 13, Item 16-17)
    - Pratt, Abby B., 1842 (Box 2, Folder 13, Item 18-19)
    - Pratt, Benaiah, 1794 (Box 2, Folder 13, Item 20)
    - Pratt, Benjamin, 1801 (Box 2, Folder 13, Item 21)
    - Pratt, Benjamin, 1842 (Box 2, Folder 13, Item 22-23)
    - Pratt, Betsey Leach, 1858 (Box 2, Folder 13, Item 24)
    - Pratt, Lucy, 1794 (Box 2, Folder 13, Item 25)
    - Pratt, Mahala, 1842 (Box 2, Folder 13, Item 26-27)
    - Pratt, Margaret, 1793 (Box 2, Folder 13, Item 28)
    - Pratt, Sarah, 1790 (Box 2, Folder 13, Item 29)
    - Pratt, Thomas, 1813 (Box 2, Folder 13, Item 30)
    - Pratt, Thomas A., 1843 (Box 2, Folder 13, Item 31)
    - Pratt, William, 1840 (Box 2, Folder 13, Item 32)
    - Pumroy, Francis Jr., 1757 (Box 2, Folder 13, Item 33)
    - Purrington, Mercy, 1763 (Box 2, Folder 13, Item 34)
    - Putnam, Harriet O., 1841 (Box 2, Folder 13, Item 35)
    - Putnam, Julia M., 1850 (Box 2, Folder 13, Item 36)
    - Putnam, Lucy, 1857 (Box 2, Folder 13, Item 37)
    - Putnam, William, 1844 (Box 2, Folder 13, Item 38)
  - Membership: R, 1750 1810; 1750-1810 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Redding, Fear, 1763 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 1)
    - Redding, Joanna, 1750 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 2)
    - Redding, Luther, 1789 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 3)
    - Redding, Thankful, 1759 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 4)
    - Ricard, Japeth, 1767 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 5)
    - Ridder, Jael, 1810 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 6)
    - Ripley, Hezekiah, 1807 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 7)
    - Ripley, Priscilla, 1807 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 8)
  - Membership: Sa-Sm, 1750 1853; 1750-1853 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Sampson, Lydia, 1808 (Box 2, Folder 15, Item 1)
    - Sampson, Samuel, 1808 (Box 2, Folder 15, Item 2)
    - Sampson, Thankful, 1782 (Box 2, Folder 2, Item 37)
    - Savery, Daniel, 1807 (Box 2, Folder 15, Item 3)
    - Savery, Huldah, 1807 (Box 2, Folder 15, Item 4)
    - Savery, Mary, 1750 (Box 2, Folder 15, Item 5)
    - Savery, Penelope, 1851 (Box 2, Folder 15, Item 6)
    - Savery, Rhoda, 1853 (Box 2, Folder 15, Item 7)
    - Savery, Thomas, 1851 (Box 2, Folder 15, Item 8)
    - Sears, Abiah, 1807 (Box 2, Folder 15, Item 9)
    - Shaw, Benjamin, 1853 (Box 2, Folder 15, Item 10)
    - Shaw, Bethiah, 1853 (Box 2, Folder 15, Item 11)
    - Shaw, Eliza, 1863 (Box 2, Folder 15, Item 12)
    - Shaw, Elizabeth, 1770 (Box 2, Folder 15, Item 13)
    - Shaw, Elkanah, 1755 (Box 2, Folder 15, Item 14)
    - Shaw, Francis Marion, 1853 (Box 2, Folder 15, Item 15)
    - Shaw, Isaac, 1802 (Box 2, Folder 15, Item 16)
    - Shaw, James, 1784 (Box 2, Folder 15, Item 17)
    - Shaw, Lois, 1784 (Box 2, Folder 15, Item 17)
    - Shaw, Lydia, 1782 (Box 2, Folder 15, Item 18)
    - Shaw, Mark, 1805 (Box 2, Folder 15, Item 19)
    - Shaw, Mary, 1771 (Box 2, Folder 15, Item 20)
    - Shaw, Samuel, 1803 1840; 1803, 1840 (Box 2, Folder 15, Item 21-22)
    - Shaw, Thomas, 1771 (Box 2, Folder 15, Item 23)
    - Shaw, William, 1782 (Box 2, Folder 15, Item 24)
    - Shurtleff, Zilpha, 1853 (Box 2, Folder 15, Item 25)
    - Smith, James, 1807 (Box 2, Folder 15, Item 26)
    - Smith, Levi, 1807 (Box 2, Folder 15, Item 27)
    - Smith, Mahala, 1840 (Box 2, Folder 15, Item 28)
    - Smith, Patience, 1807 (Box 2, Folder 15, Item 29)
    - Smith, Susanna, 1783 (Box 2, Folder 15, Item 30)
    - Smith, Susanna B., 1850 (Box 2, Folder 15, Item 31)
  - Membership: Sn-Sw, 1782 1865; 1782-1865 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Snow, Olive, 1859 (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 1)
    - Soule, Alfred B., 1841 (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 2)
    - Soule, Amanda, 1865 (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 3)
    - Soule, Augustus H., 1865 (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 4)
    - Soule, Hannah, 1850 (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 5)
    - Soule, Irene, 1837 (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 6)
    - Soule, Isaac III, 1840 (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 7-9)
    - Soule, James II, 1807 (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 10)
    - Soule, Joanna, 1807 (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 11)
    - Soule, John, 1807 (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 12)
    - Soule, Lydia, 1782 (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 13)
    - Soule, Marcia, 1850 (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 14)
    - Soule, Priscilla, 1840 (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 15)
    - Soule, Rebecca, 1840 (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 16)
    - Soule, Sarah, 1782 (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 17)
    - Sparrow, Edward, 1804 (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 18)
    - Sparrow, Josiah, 1808 (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 19)
    - Sparrow, Minerva, 1808 (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 20)
    - Sproat, Mary, 1824 (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 21)
    - Standish, Irene, 1808 (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 22)
    - Standish, Jane, 1829 (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 23)
    - Sturtevant, Abigail, 1808 (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 24)
    - Sturtevant, Eunice, 1813 (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 25)
    - Sturtevant, Priscilla, 1813 (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 26)
    - Sturtevant, Sarah, 1795 (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 27)
    - Swift, Lucy, 1814 (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 28)
  - Membership: Thomas, 1763 1853; 1763-1853 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Thomas, Abigail, 1789 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 1)
    - Thomas, Anna, 1831 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 2)
    - Thomas, Azel, 1824 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 3)
    - Thomas, Betsey, 1807 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 4)
    - Thomas, Betsey, 1829 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 5)
    - Thomas, Betsey C., 1815 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 6)
    - Thomas, Churchill, 1781 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 7)
    - Thomas, Clarissa Jane, 1853 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 8)
    - Thomas, Daniel, 1780 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 9)
    - Thomas, David, 1781 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 10)
    - Thomas, Deborah, 1782 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 11)
    - Thomas, Edward, 1807 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 12)
    - Thomas, Eleazer, 1824 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 13)
    - Thomas, Eunice, 1831 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 14)
    - Thomas, Hannah, 1831 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 15)
    - Thomas, Hope, 1808 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 16)
    - Thomas, Hope, 1831 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 17)
    - Thomas, Huldah, 1831 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 18)
    - Thomas, Jacob, 1808 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 19)
    - Thomas, Kezia, 1771 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 20)
    - Thomas, Lamuel, 1763 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 21)
    - Thomas, Lothrop, 1838 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 22)
    - Thomas, Louisa, 1838 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 23)
    - Thomas, Lucia, 1831 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 24)
    - Thomas, Lucia (Lucy), 1763 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 25)
    - Thomas, Lucy, 1808 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 26)
    - Thomas, Lydia, 1807 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 27)
    - Thomas, Mary, 1807 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 28)
    - Thomas, Mary Ann, 1838 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 29)
    - Thomas, Mary H., 1838 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 30)
    - Thomas, Melinda, 1853 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 31)
    - Thomas, Mercy, 1782 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 32)
    - Thomas, Nathan, 1792 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 33)
    - Thomas, Perez, 1803 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 34)
    - Thomas, Phebe, 1824 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 35)
    - Thomas, Phebe, 1842 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 36)
    - Thomas, Saba S., 1838 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 37)
    - Thomas, Seneca, 1831 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 38)
    - Thomas, Seneca R., 1853 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 39)
    - Thomas, Serena, 1814 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 40)
    - Thomas, Silas, 1824 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 41)
    - Thomas, Susanna, 1809 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 42)
    - Thomas, Sylvanus, 1809 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 43)
    - Thomas, Thankful, 1783 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 44)
    - Thomas, William, 1807 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 45)
    - Thomas, Winslow, 1831 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 46)
    - Thomas, Zenas, 1807 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 27)
    - Thomas, Zilpah, 1798 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 47)
    - Thomas, Zilpah, 1853 (Box 2, Folder 17, Item 48)
  - Membership: Thompson, 1799 1880; 1799-1880 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Thompson, Alfred, 1858 (Box 2, Folder 18, Item 1)
    - Thompson, Angeline, 1858 (Box 2, Folder 18, Item 2)
    - Thompson, Ann, 1840 (Box 2, Folder 18, Item 3)
    - Thompson, Annie Eliza, 1858 (Box 2, Folder 18, Item 4)
    - Thompson, Benjamin, 1840 (Box 2, Folder 18, Item 5)
    - Thompson, Cephas, 1832 (Box 2, Folder 18, Item 6)
    - Thompson, Charles, 1831 (Box 2, Folder 18, Item 7)
    - Thompson, Charles L., 1858 1880; 1858, 1880 (Box 2, Folder 18, Item 8-9)
    - Thompson, Eliza G., 1858 (Box 2, Folder 18, Item 10)
    - Thompson, Ellen, 1863 (Box 2, Folder 18, Item 11)
    - Thompson, Ezra, 1808 (Box 2, Folder 18, Item 12)
    - Thompson, Florantha, 1831 (Box 2, Folder 18, Item 13)
    - Thompson, Franklin, 1857 (Box 2, Folder 18, Item 14)
    - Thompson, Ivory B., 1858 (Box 2, Folder 18, Item 15)
    - Thompson, Ivory H., 1858 (Box 2, Folder 18, Item 16)
    - Thompson, Jane, 1840 (Box 2, Folder 18, Item 17)
    - Thompson, Jerusha, 1858 (Box 2, Folder 18, Item 18)
    - Thompson, Lucia A., 1863 (Box 2, Folder 18, Item 19)
    - Thompson, Lucy, 1808 (Box 2, Folder 18, Item 20)
    - Thompson, Lydia, 1806 (Box 2, Folder 18, Item 21)
    - Thompson, Lydia, 1808 (Box 2, Folder 18, Item 22)
    - Thompson, Mary Elizabeth, 1858 (Box 2, Folder 18, Item 23)
    - Thompson, Nathaniel, 1807 (Box 2, Folder 18, Item 24)
    - Thompson, Otis, 1799 (Box 2, Folder 18, Item 25)
    - Thompson, Philander, 1858 (Box 2, Folder 18, Item 26)
    - Thompson, Philander W., 1858 (Box 2, Folder 18, Item 27)
    - Thompson, Polly, 1808 (Box 2, Folder 18, Item 28)
    - Thompson, Reuel, 1807 (Box 2, Folder 18, Item 29)
    - Thompson, Reuel F., 1863 (Box 2, Folder 18, Item 30)
    - Thompson, Sarah, 1841 (Box 2, Folder 18, Item 31)
    - Thompson, Venus, 1840 (Box 2, Folder 18, Item 32)
    - Thompson, Weltha, 1806 (Box 2, Folder 18, Item 33)
  - Membership: Thu-Tu, 1764 1861; 1764-1861 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Thurston, Francis, 1857 (Box 2, Folder 19, Item 1)
    - Tilson, Amanda, 1861 (Box 2, Folder 19, Item 2)
    - Tilson, Calvin, 1803 (Box 2, Folder 19, Item 3)
    - Tilson, Calvin Jr., 1807 (Box 2, Folder 19, Item 4)
    - Tilson, Hannah, 1808 (Box 2, Folder 19, Item 5)
    - Tilson, Joanna, 1804 (Box 2, Folder 19, Item 6)
    - Tilson, Silence, 1764 (Box 2, Folder 19, Item 7)
    - Tiner, Sarah, 1853 (Box 2, Folder 19, Item 8)
    - Tinkham, Anna, 1807 (Box 2, Folder 19, Item 9)
    - Tinkham, Barbara, 1829 (Box 2, Folder 19, Item 10)
    - Tinkham, Betsey, 1840 (Box 2, Folder 19, Item 11)
    - Tinkham, Chloe, 1782 (Box 2, Folder 19, Item 12)
    - Tinkham, Elizabeth, 1794 (Box 2, Folder 19, Item 13)
    - Tinkham, Hannah, 1765 (Box 2, Folder 19, Item 14)
    - Tinkham, Harvey, 1840 (Box 2, Folder 19, Item 11)
    - Tinkham, Jane, 1840 (Box 2, Folder 19, Item 15)
    - Tinkham, Jeremiah, 1787 (Box 2, Folder 19, Item 16)
    - Tinkham, John, 1813 (Box 2, Folder 19, Item 17)
    - Tinkham, Lucy, 1785 (Box 2, Folder 19, Item 18)
    - Tinkham, Lydia Ann, 1858 (Box 2, Folder 19, Item 19)
    - Tinkham, Molly, 1789 (Box 2, Folder 19, Item 20)
    - Tinkham, Oliver, 1840 (Box 2, Folder 19, Item 21)
    - Tinkham, Orin, 1814 (Box 2, Folder 19, Item 22)
    - Tinkham, Ruth, 1785 (Box 2, Folder 19, Item 23)
    - Tinkham, Sarah, 1796 (Box 2, Folder 19, Item 24)
    - Tinkham, Sarah Jane, 1850 (Box 2, Folder 19, Item 25)
    - Tinkham, Silas, 1807 (Box 2, Folder 19, Item 26)
    - Tinkham, Squire, 1807 (Box 2, Folder 19, Item 27)
    - Tisdale, Hannah, 1807 (Box 2, Folder 19, Item 28)
    - Tisdale, Jacob, 1791 (Box 2, Folder 19, Item 29)
    - Tomson, Caleb Jr., 1784 (Box 2, Folder 19, Item 30)
    - Tomson, Deborah, 1786 (Box 2, Folder 19, Item 31)
    - Tomson, Freelove, 1786 (Box 2, Folder 19, Item 32)
    - Tomson, Irene, 1808 (Box 2, Folder 19, Item 33)
    - Tomson, Isaac, 1786 (Box 2, Folder 19, Item 34)
    - Tomson, Lucy, 1786 (Box 2, Folder 19, Item 35)
    - Tomson, Molly, 1784 (Box 2, Folder 19, Item 36)
    - Tomson, William, 1786 (Box 2, Folder 19, Item 30)
    - Torrey, Mary, 1787 (Box 2, Folder 19, Item 37)
    - Torrey, Samuel, 1787 (Box 2, Folder 19, Item 38)
    - Trebou, Bathsheba, 1807 (Box 2, Folder 19, Item 39)
    - Tucker, Benjamin Jr., 1776 (Box 2, Folder 19, Item 40)
    - Tucker, Hannah, 1810 (Box 2, Folder 19, Item 41)
    - Tucker, Jedidah, 1809 (Box 2, Folder 19, Item 42)
    - Tucker, Mandana, 1830 (Box 2, Folder 19, Item 43)
    - Tucker, Samuel, 1797 (Box 2, Folder 19, Item 44)
    - Turner, Priscilla, 1794 (Box 2, Folder 19, Item 45)
  - Membership: V, 1763 1853; 1763-1853 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Valler, Mercy, 1791 (Box 2, Folder 20, Item 1)
    - Vaugh, Abraham, 1763 (Box 2, Folder 20, Item 2)
    - Vaughn, Lucy, 1783 (Box 2, Folder 20, Item 3)
    - Vaughn, Salome, 1853 (Box 2, Folder 20, Item 4)
    - Vineca, Dorlisca, 1840 (Box 2, Folder 20, Item 5)
    - Vineca, Lydia, 1841 (Box 2, Folder 20, Item 6)
    - Vineca, Rachel, 1840 (Box 2, Folder 20, Item 7)
  - Membership: Wa-Wi, 1758 1863; 1758-1863 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Warren, Betsey, 1829 (Box 2, Folder 21, Item 1)
    - Warren, George, 1842 (Box 2, Folder 21, Item 2)
    - Warren, John, 1807 (Box 2, Folder 21, Item 3)
    - Warren, Joseph, 1763 (Box 2, Folder 21, Item 4)
    - Warren, Keziah, 1806 (Box 2, Folder 21, Item 5)
    - Washburn, Azel, 1782 (Box 2, Folder 21, Item 6)
    - Washburn, Elizabeth, 1837 (Box 2, Folder 21, Item 7)
    - Washburn, Eunice, 1840 (Box 2, Folder 21, Item 8)
    - Washburn, Huldah, 1774 (Box 2, Folder 21, Item 9)
    - Weston, Hannah, 1813 (Box 2, Folder 21, Item 10)
    - Weston, Isaiah, 1793 (Box 2, Folder 21, Item 11)
    - Weston, John, 1812 (Box 2, Folder 21, Item 12)
    - Weston, Mary, 1859 (Box 2, Folder 21, Item 13)
    - Weston, Priscilla, 1784 (Box 2, Folder 21, Item 14)
    - Weston, Priscilla, 1809 (Box 2, Folder 21, Item 15)
    - Weston, Salome, 1813 (Box 2, Folder 21, Item 16)
    - Weston, Thomas Jr., 1853 (Box 2, Folder 21, Item 17)
    - Wilbur, Perry, 1842 (Box 2, Folder 21, Item 18)
    - Wilder, Bathsheba, 1841 (Box 2, Folder 21, Item 19)
    - Wilder, Ebenezer, 1799 (Box 2, Folder 21, Item 20)
    - Wilder, Mary, 1808 (Box 2, Folder 21, Item 21)
    - Wilder, Polly, 1808 (Box 2, Folder 21, Item 22)
    - Wilder, Susannah, 1809 (Box 2, Folder 21, Item 23)
    - Williams, Helen, 1863 (Box 2, Folder 21, Item 24)
    - Williams, Jabez, 1813 (Box 2, Folder 21, Item 25)
    - Willis, Ebenezer, 1758 (Box 2, Folder 21, Item 26)
    - Willis, Mary, 1758 (Box 2, Folder 21, Item 26)
    - Willis, Mary Jane, 1859 (Box 2, Folder 21, Item 27)
    - Wing, Lauretta, 1829 1843; 1829, 1843 (Box 2, Folder 21, Item 28-29)
  - Membership: Wo-Wr, 1773 1858; 1773-1858 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Wood, Abiel, 1842 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 1)
    - Wood, Abigail, 1808 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 2)
    - Wood, Abigail, 1840 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 3)
    - Wood, Betsey, 1813 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 4)
    - Wood, Charles W., 1837 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 5)
    - Wood, Eleanor, 1842 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 6)
    - Wood, Elizabeth, 1776 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 7)
    - Wood, Elizabeth, 1809 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 8)
    - Wood, Emily L., 1837 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 9)
    - Wood, Ichabod, 1808 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 10)
    - Wood, Ichabod, 1814 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 11)
    - Wood, Israel, 1809 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 12)
    - Wood, Lucy, 1807 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 13)
    - Wood, Lydia, 1807 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 14)
    - Wood, Maria, 1807 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 15)
    - Wood, Maria A., 1863 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 16)
    - Wood, Mary, 1814 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 17)
    - Wood, Mary, 1842 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 18)
    - Wood, Mary C., 1841 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 19)
    - Wood, Mary F., 1858 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 20)
    - Wood, Mary T., 1837 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 21)
    - Wood, Mercy L., 1841 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 22)
    - Wood, Pauline T., 1858 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 23)
    - Wood, Rebecca, 1782 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 24)
    - Wood, Sarah, 1807 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 25)
    - Wood, Theodore, 1809 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 26)
    - Wood, Wilkes, 1837 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 27)
    - Wood, William H., 1837 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 28)
    - Wright, Anna, 1796 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 29)
    - Wright, Cuffy, 1773 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 30)
    - Wrightington, Henry, 1858 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 31)
    - Wrightington, Hope, 1844 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 32)
  - Marriage intentions: A-C, 1837 1849; 1837-1849 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - George Adams and Abby A. Eddy, 1844 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 1)
    - Caleb Alden and Abigail Tinkham, 1838 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 2)
    - Theodore H. Alden and Mary E. Murdoch, 1849 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 3)
    - Isaac Alger and Lucy Pierce, 1841 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 4-5)
    - Levi Atwood Jr. and Adaline Shurtleff, 1842 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 6)
    - Stephen Atwood and Elizabeth Atwood, 1842 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 7-8)
    - Tillson Atwood and Ruth Tillson, 1839 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 9)
    - Ira R. Bailey and Marcia W. Chace, 1844 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 10-11)
    - Thomas F. Barden and Eleanor H. Tinkham, 1837 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 12)
    - Edward G. Barrows and Serena A. Shaw, 1847 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 13)
    - Nathan C. Barrows and Phebe G. Wilber, 1849 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 14)
    - Gilbert M. Benson and Abigail L. Bump, 1845 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 15)
    - George C. Boomer and Elizabeth Savory, 1843 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 16-17)
    - John L. Bowman and Sarah Warren, 1844 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 18)
    - Charles W. Bradford and Bethania W. LeBarron, 1846 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 19)
    - Winslow Bradford and Fanny S. Atwood, 1846 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 20-21)
    - Ebenezer E. Bailey and Melinda Horton, 1838 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 22-23)
    - Bradford Braley and Lucy C. Bump, 1848 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 24-25)
    - James W. Briggs and Aseneth Lucas, 1849 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 26)
    - Arad Bryant and Betsey Simmons, 1848 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 27)
    - Ira Bryant and Mercy E. Freeman, 1845 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 28)
    - Phillander Bryant and Jane Pinkham, 1843 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 29)
    - Isaac D. Bump and Julia A. Pope, 1842 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 30)
    - Winslow Burgess and Elizabeth C. Thomas, 1839 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 31-32)
    - R. Spaugheim Capen and Mary L. Atwood, 1847 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 33)
    - Orlando W. Carver and Hannah C. Thomas, 1847 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 34)
    - Abiather Caswell III and Lydia C. Chase, 1837 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 35)
    - Cyrus P. Caswell abd Betsey Warren, 1842 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 36)
    - Eliab Caswell and Eliza Thomas, 1839 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 37)
    - Ezra S Chase and Sarah Coggshall, 1844 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 38)
    - George A. Churchill and Amarantha J. Burgess, 1842 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 39)
    - Nathan Cobb and Deborah Murdoch, 1838 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 40)
    - Timothy Cobb and Jane E. Eddy, 1841 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 41-42)
    - Eliezer Cole and Rebecca Swift, 1841 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 43)
    - Hezakiah Cole and Deborah Freeman, 1843 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 44-45)
    - James Cole Jr. and Bulia A. T. Macomber, 1845 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 46)
    - William O. Cornish and Hannah Tinkham, 1838 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 47)
    - William O. Cornish and Susannah B. Wood, 1845 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 48)
    - Ephraim Curtis and Malinda Wood, 1840 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 49-50)
    - Abner W. Cushman and Ann Maria Chase, 1847 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 51)
    - Samuel Cushman and Betsey A Raymond, 1842 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 52)
  - Marriage intentions: D-M, 1837 1852; 1837-1852 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Nathan S. Davis and Maria A. Wood, 1849 (Box 2, Folder 24, Item 1)
    - William Darling and Sarah W. Wood, 1847 (Box 2, Folder 24, Item 2)
    - Ellis Delano and Jane E. Standish, 1840 (Box 2, Folder 24, Item 3-4)
    - Joseph Dunham and Mary S. Gibbs, 1840 (Box 2, Folder 24, Item 5-6)
    - Alden Eaton and Harriet K. Lincoln, 1843 (Box 2, Folder 24, Item 7)
    - William L. Eddy and Adeline H. Osgood, 1847 (Box 2, Folder 24, Item 8)
    - Eliphalet Elmes and Esther M. Morton, 1841 (Box 2, Folder 24, Item 9)
    - Theodore Elmes and Sarah E. Gay, 1842 (Box 2, Folder 24, Item 10-11)
    - John L. Everett and Hanna B. Nelson, 1844 (Box 2, Folder 24, Item 12)
    - E. Copeland Fales and Mary Jane Fuller, 1846 (Box 2, Folder 24, Item 13-14)
    - Benjamin Freeman and Nancy C. Fuller, 1846 (Box 2, Folder 24, Item 15)
    - Elisha E. Freeman and Betsey P. Standish, 1839 (Box 2, Folder 24, Item 16)
    - Samuel Freeman and Anna B. Tinkham, 1838 (Box 2, Folder 24, Item 17)
    - Timothy Freeman and Emeline L. Lincoln, 1848 (Box 2, Folder 24, Item 18-19)
    - Cyrus Fuller and Mary F. Thompson, 1841 (Box 2, Folder 24, Item 20-21)
    - Ebenezer Fuller and Mary Ann Colwell, 1842 (Box 2, Folder 24, Item 22-23)
    - Nathan Fuller Jr. and Sarah Fuller, 1842 (Box 2, Folder 24, Item 24-25)
    - Erastus E. Gay and Susan M. Brown, 1848 (Box 2, Folder 24, Item 26)
    - Bernard Glancy and Patience Gammans, 1839 (Box 2, Folder 24, Item 27)
    - Joseph F. Hammond and Luranz K. Harlon, 1845 (Box 2, Folder 24, Item 28-29)
    - Lewis Harlow and Betsey Briggs, 1842 (Box 2, Folder 24, Item 30)
    - Lewis Harlow Jr. and Elizabeth Briggs, 1845 (Box 2, Folder 24, Item 31)
    - Reuben Harlow and Betsey Shaw, 1841 (Box 2, Folder 24, Item 32)
    - Isaac G. Harrington and Hanna S. Baker, 1845 (Box 2, Folder 24, Item 33-34)
    - Rupel L. Hathaway and Mary Wood, 1843 (Box 2, Folder 24, Item 35-36)
    - Sahum W. Hill and Jemina Newel, 1846 (Box 2, Folder 24, Item 37-38)
    - Truman C. Holmes and Betsey Cobb, 1838 (Box 2, Folder 24, Item 39-40)
    - Davis W. Howard and Abby Darling, 1846 (Box 2, Folder 24, Item 41-42)
    - John F. Howland and Mercy Tinkham, 1844 (Box 2, Folder 24, Item 43-44)
    - John William Hunt and Rouette L. Thompson, 1848 (Box 2, Folder 24, Item 45-46)
    - Watson Jenny and Harriet A. Gibbs, 1852 (Box 2, Folder 24, Item 47)
    - Nathan King and Ellen Thompson, 1841 (Box 2, Folder 24, Item 48)
    - William A. King and Lucy A. Thompson, 1844 (Box 2, Folder 24, Item 49)
    - Tiba LeBarron and Sarah B. Shaw, 1845 (Box 2, Folder 24, Item 50)
    - George Leonard and Lydia Gammons, 1841 (Box 2, Folder 24, Item 51)
    - Tisdale Leonard and Emily A. Howard, 1845 (Box 2, Folder 24, Item 52)
    - William L. Lincoln and Juliette E. Sherman, 1846 (Box 2, Folder 24, Item 53)
    - Lemuel Lyon and Cintha M. Beals, 1837 (Box 2, Folder 24, Item 54)
    - Amasa Merill and Elizabeth Tinkham, 1839 (Box 2, Folder 24, Item 55)
    - Abishai Miller and Julia Ann Sparrow, 1838 (Box 2, Folder 24, Item 56)